goalview.com 2010-03-26

# GoalView - Privacy Policy

|   
|   
|   
| Public Consulting Group Web Site Privacy Policy Public Consulting Group considers your personal information to be your private property and subject to your control. We are committed to protecting your privacy. The following statements outline: 

  * The type of information we may collect when you visit our web site 
  * How we plan to use any collected information 
  * The Public Consulting Group policy regarding the sharing of collected information **What Information is Collected**  

When you link to the Public Consulting Group web site and browse its contents, we do not automatically collect personal information from or about you. By personal information, we mean such data as your name, mailing address, telephone numbers, social security number and email address.

On those pages where we provide specific links to the Public Consulting Group or personnel, you may be asked to supply some elements of your personal information. If you are visiting those pages and choose to send us information about yourself, you do so voluntarily. On our part, we will hold this information in confidence. We will reveal such information only if we are legally required to do so or if you specifically request and approve the release of the information.

You will find links from the Public Consulting Group site to independently owned, controlled, and/or managed Web sites whose content we believe will be of possible interest and value to our visitors. Additionally, you will see links from advertisers, sponsors, and other partners who may use Public Consulting Group logo as part of a co-branding agreement.

In many cases, these links represent cooperative projects or mutual links established with the organizations connected with these sites. We do not control the content of these links. These other sites may send you their own cookies, collect data, or solicit personal information. We do not control these cookies or the content of these third parties.

**How the Collected Information is Used**  
Any information that we collect from you on the Public Consulting Group site will only be used to: 

    * Respond to your request for product information 
    * Register you for a Public Consulting Group workshop 
    * Register you for a Public Consulting Group contest 
    * Consider you for a Public Consulting Groupl job opening 

**Information Sharing Policy**  
Public Consulting Group maintains a policy of not sharing any data collected on the web site with anyone outside of Public Consulting Group. The only exceptions to this policy occur when we are legally required to reveal such information or when you specifically request and approve that the information be released.

The importance of security for your personally identifiable information is of utmost concern to us. We have systems in place to assist us in providing secure transmission of your information from your PC to our servers. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information, Public Consulting Group cannot and does not ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us, and you do so at your own risk.

Please contact us at [info@pcgus.com](mailto:info@pcgus.com) for more information.   
  
---|---|---|---
